<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data name="Revolution" author="Thumblegudget, Bredroll, QuantX" description="

The Revolution mod brings Radar to Needlefish, ECM to aircraft and introduces a more immersive fog-of-war for island captures.

The mod is based on UI Enhancer and Albatross AWACS, so you get those amazing benefits included.

[h2]ECM[/h2]

Aircraft can now equip an ECM Mission Pod on wing hardpoints. In addition to 1000l of fuel, these pods provide Radar jamming and spoofing
capability.  When fitted they will reduce the distance where a hostile Radar will pick up the aircraft.  If fitted to an AWACS, the pod will
the emeny Radar to see multiple ghost contacts.

ECM reduces the contact range to about 8km from the carrier, AWACS or ground based radars.

[h2]Enhanced Radar Simulations[/h2]

[list]
[*] AWACS Radar now has increased range if you fly above 1600m, up to a max of 12km.
[*] Radar ground clutter is now considered when tracking aircraft.
[*] Flying at below 20m you can potentially sneak in under Radar.
[*] It is also harder to detect aircraft flying low over very rough sea.
[*] CIWS Needlefish can detect hostile aircraft at 5km
[*] Torpedo Needlefish can detect ships at 3.5km
[*] Cruise Missile Needlefish can detect ships at 6km
[*] Gun Needlefish can detect ships at 2km
[*] All Needlefish can see ships and aircraft that are closer than 0.5km.
[/list]



[h2]Fog of War[/h2]

The color (team) of a hostile island will be hidden until you bring a unit within range of that island. No more will capturing an AI controlled 
island give away your position 100km away.

[h2]Markers[/h2]

You can now add markers to the game map to help your team plan and keep track of information and objectives.  Place up
to 4 point markers on the map that will be viewable by all your crew on operator screen terminals or holomaps.

[h2]Holomap Quick Select[/h2]

The holomap now has an expandable menu that can be used to select and zoom to friendly aircraft. Useful if your
captain is acting as GCI to select the aircraft of a player needing guidance.

[h2]Aircraft Cam and Petrel Orders[/h2]

For aircraft, if you click one on the holomap, you can now see an
extra menu, clicking Camera will show a low-res version of the aircraft
flight camera

If you click a Petrel, you will be able to click the Airlift button to
order it to pickup the nearest friendly ground unit within 700m

If the petrel is carrying cargo already, you will be able to click to deploy
the unit at the petrel's current location.

[h2]General Info[/h2]

This is merged with 2 other mods:

Albatross AWACS swaps the AWACS-carrying capability from the Manta to the Albatross - By Thumblegudget
Also includes UI enhancer - By QuantX
">
</data>