<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data name="Revolution 1.2" author="Thumblegudget, Bredroll, QuantX" description="
The Revolution mod (v1.2) brings Radar enhancements and introduces a more immersive fog-of-war for island
captures.

For fully details on what the mod does, how you can contribute or request features see
[url=https://cc2maps.com/revolution-mod/]https://cc2maps.com/revolution-mod/[/url]

The mod is based on UI Enhancer and Albatross AWACS, so you get those amazing benefits included.

[h2]Enhanced Radar Sim[/h2]

[list]
[*] Manta can fly in 'stealth' configuration if you fit smaller/fewer hardpoint attachments, significantly reduce
   their RADAR detection range.
[*] Razorbill and Manta gain a RWR that can detect hostile radar sources
[*] Razorbill gains the option of using a twin barrelled nose mounted gun
[*] Walrus can now use the 100mm heavy cannon
[*] Bear can now mount TV missiles on it's utility slots.
[*] AWACS now has increased range if you fly above 1600m, up to a max of 12km.
[*] Ground clutter/wave height are now considered when tracking low level aircraft in operator screens.
[*] Flying below 40-50m you can try sneak in under your opponent's Radar.
[*] CIWS fish can detect hostile aircraft at 5km
[*] Torpedo fish can detect ships at 3.5km
[*] Cruise Missile fish can detect ships at 6km
[*] Gun fish can detect ships at 2km
[*] All Needlefish can see ships and aircraft that are closer than 0.5km.
[*] AWACS and Golfball RADAR HUDs now show useful tactical air-map details
[/list]

[h2]Fog of War[/h2]

The color (team) of a hostile island will be hidden until you bring a unit within range of it. No more will
capturing an AI controlled island give away your position 100km away.

[h2]Barge Cap[/h2]

[list]
[*] Barge islands now serve as control nodes for your barges, each island lets you control two extra barges (plus a base two to start with)
[*] Barge camera (HUD) video streams can be jammed by enemy carriers. If your barge gets very close (<200m) to a hostile carrier, you will get increasingly more signal degredation until your video drops out.
[/list]

For example:
If your team has 2 carriers, and you control 2 barge islands, you will be able to build a maximum of 1 + 2 + 4 = 7 barges.
If your team has 1 carrier, and one barge island, you'll be able to build no more than 1 + 1 + 2 = 4 total barges.

If you lose an island or carrier, your barges won't go away, you just won't be able to build more than the cap for what
you have.

[h2]General Info[/h2]

This is merged with 2 other mods:

Albatross AWACS swaps the AWACS-carrying capability from the Manta to the Albatross - By Thumblegudget
Also includes UI enhancer - By QuantX

[h2]Credits[/h2]

Thank-you to QuantX for UI Enhancer. And to Mr Scoot for showing how deep you can dive with modding CC2.

Thanks also to Kazzik, CylindricalBobcat, Thumblegudget, RolandLoop, Pupboy1000 and Pointclearius and Delta Fleet for help testing the mod.

">
</data>